what's going on guys so I wanted to talk
about the new toy that I got and I hung
up in my garage I needed something new
to play with during a lot of stuck at
home during isolation and so I have
heavy bags at my gym and I could still
go there but I didn't want to haul a
heavy bag home or mounted a heavy bag
rack so I wanted something simple and
this is something that I've always
wanted to kind of work on and train with
but me being a Muay Thai guy or Muay
Thai kickboxing instructor that is not
it's not a tool that we generally use
okay
I do work on boxing as well so it's just
a way to sharpen up one of my skills
that I don't have a lot of time to do at
the gym when I'm at my gym and I'm
teaching my classes of course I'm
teaching Muay Thai so there's a lot more
kicking and that type of striking and
again we do not use dublin bags or speed
bags or anything of that sort so why not
put one of these up instead of trying to
order a heavy bag or bring the whole a
heavy bag home and i've had a blast with
this thing check it out
so the installation is not hard I
thought it would be a lot harder than it
was so if you look up here all I ended
up doing was screwing a hook a self
screwing hook big hook actually we used
to use this to hang up our bicycle I
screwed that into a stud up there in the
top of my garage and then it comes with
two bungees these bungees here and so I
hooked one up there and then also what
they come with are these adjustable
strings here which are pretty cool you
push this button and then you're able to
pull the string to the tightness you
need which helps you really determine it
get the exact height that you want I
thought that was pretty cool so title
sends you two of these bungees and one
of these Pro adjustable Pro grips that
you can pull to the adjustable height
now I know some people don't like those
because they feel like it affects the
give on the bag cuz with two bungees it
moves a lot better and some people don't
like that there's this is a string it's
not really any kind of bungee of any
sort but I didn't see a problem with it
at all
it has the perfect amount of give once I
was able to pull it adjust it down here
to the exact height now if you noticed I
used two dumbbells to anchor it and
that's because this is my garage and my
wife didn't want it something would only
allow me to put something temporary in
the garage because when everything is
said and done in the winter time she
wants me to be able to pull the cars
into the garage so she didn't want me I
know that a lot of people anchor like an
eye hook into the ground to hook the
other the bottom end in but that's much
more permanent and so this is just an
easy solution you know now I could just
pick up the dumbbells and tip you know
listen to program and just pull the hook
off the top I mean I can put it up and
take it down as fast as I want it's very
easy so it keep it makes it temporary
again my wife is not really looking to
allow me to really do anything permit if
you want a permanent you're free to go
ahead and drill into your
three but that's just not something I
needed to do for this one I think that's
what makes the makes it really cool is
how easy it is to put up a takedown okay
but you again you want to make sure
you're getting the height just right so
I like my double end bag I got my chin
then again that that program strap makes
it so easy to adjust it any and like I
said as far as the give it has just the
right amount for me when I had I did try
both punches I did try that and it was
you know I just didn't feel right you
know and then plus the height ended up
up here and I didn't have a way to
adjust it I would have had to tie knots
in the bungees which I've seen some
people do so I think that's very cool
that title includes those grips for you
to kind of get exactly what you're
looking for I know some people just go
to the store and buy actual bungee and
tie it up and get the right height but
that's not what I was looking to do this
is just very simple sorta you know they
it all comes with the purchase so
another thing you want to look at is
here because if you look up there the
hook looks like he could slip off so I
just didn't want it when I was doing
uppercuts and whatnot I didn't want this
hook slipping on so this is just simple
man I just took some some of duct tape
it just taped it around so that this the
ring wouldn't pop off the hook so
nothing super fancy but very very simple
fix so to sum things up man this is a
great purchase I think total it was 38
dollars total with tax and shipping and
everything 38 dollars man during
isolation I know a lot of students and
friends were running out to buy heavy
bags to come because they were stuck at
home training you're spending hundreds
of dollars when something as simple as
this you can use to really sharpen your
striking skills so even you know after
well you know the stay at home orders
lifted or whatever and you get back this
is something and now I'm trying to my
wife and I were trying to figure out a
way how we're gonna get this put up in
the gym we'd have to take down one of
our bags to get this up but I am in love
with this thing and now it's gonna be
integrated as like a tool in my
consistent to excuse me in my training
so yeah
if you've been considering it it's a
great purchase oh one thing I forgot to
mention make sure you have like a ball
pump okay cuz there's a little hole
right there and that's how you pump it
up and I didn't have a ball pump I
thought I did but my bicycle pump did
not have the little needle so I had to
order one of those and wait a couple
days because it's not good until we get
one so make sure you have that and
that's the last piece man otherwise this
is easy installation and a whole lot of
fun man so I highly recommend this
alright remember keep fighting for fit
and no excuses man alright we'll see you
in the next video